Terror... that screams from the grave!
The Undead is a horror, fantasy film directed by Roger Corman.
Two psychics place a prostitute under hypnosis in order
to learn about her past-life experiences.
When they unwittingly send her back in time, she finds herself in the Middle
Ages, suspected of being a witch and on the verge of being executed.
Diana Love / Helene, played by Pamela Duncan.
Pendragon, played by Richard Garland.
Livia, played by Allison Hayes.
Quintus Ratcliff, played by Val Dufour.
Gravedigger Smolkin, played by Mel Welles.
Meg Maud, played by Dorothy Neumann.
The Undead is a 1957 horror film directed by Roger Corman and starring
Pamela Duncan, Allison Hayes, Richard Garland and Val Dufour.
It also features Corman regulars Richard Devon, Dick
Miller, Mel Welles and Bruno VeSota.
The authors' original working title was The Trance of Diana Love.
The film  follows the story of a prostitute, Diana Love (Duncan), who is put into a hypnotic
trance by psychic Quintus (Dufour), thus causing her to regress to a previous life.
Hayes later starred in Attack of the 50 Foot Woman (1958).
The film was released on February 14, 1957 by American
International Pictures as a double feature with Voodoo Woman.
The film explores themes of witch, coffin, spider, reincarnation, femme fatale.
The tone is dark.